W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, 1916-1981, undated; 2
  - Department of Agriculture, 1916-1981, undated; 1
    - Marshall and Marshall Cotton Company, Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 59)
    - Molasses, Correspondence and Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 69, Folder 60)
    - Morrison Milling Company, Correspondence and Remarks, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 61)
    - National Beef Council, Statement, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 62)
    - National Turkey Marketing Order, Surveys, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 63)
    - Newsletters, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 64)
    - Nicaraguan Cattle, Booklet, 1969 November (Box 69, Folder 65)
    - Office of the Secretary, Addresses (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Office of the Secretary, Addresses (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Secretary, Addresses, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Office of the Secretary, Addresses, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Secretary, Addresses, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Office of the Secretary, Background Information, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Office of the Secretary, Comments, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Office of the Secretary, Comments, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Office of the Secretary, Excerpts, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Office of the Secretary, Excerpts, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Office of the Secretary, Paper, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Office of the Secretary, Paper, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Office of the Secretary, Presentations, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Office of the Secretary, Press Releases, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (1 of 6), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (2 of 6), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (3 of 6), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (4 of 6), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (5 of 6), 1978 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks (6 of 6), 1978 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Secretary, Remarks, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Office of the Secretary, Speeches, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Secretary, Speeches, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Office of the Secretary, Speeches, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Office of the Secretary, Statements (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Office of the Secretary, Statements (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Office of the Secretary, Statements, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Office of the Secretary, Statements, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Office of the Secretary, Statements (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Office of the Secretary, Statements (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Secretary, Statements, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Office of the Secretary, Summaries, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Secretary, Testimonies, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Organizational Charts, 1969 (Box 149 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Paper, “Rural Recreational Developments”, 11th Congressional District, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Parity Prices, Correspondence and Essays, 1940-1941 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Parity Prices, Reports, 1935-1941 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Peanut Lab, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Peanut Lab, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Peanut Lab, Reports and Statements, 1962-1963 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Peanuts, Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Periodical, “American Youth”, 1971 May/June (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Personnel, Clippings and Rosters, 1965, undated (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Petitions, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, circa 1970 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Plantation Foods, Incorporated, Memoranda, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Poage-Aiken Bill, Clippings and Legal Complaint, 1966-1967, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Poage-Aiken Bill, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Poage-Aiken Bill, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Poage-Aiken Bill, Legislative Reports and Pamphlets, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Poage-Aiken Bill, Statements, 1966-1967, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Printed Materials, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Printed Materials, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Printed Materials and Reports, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Printed Materials, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Printed Materials, 1970-1973 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Printed Materials, 1974-1978 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Production and Marketing Administration, Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Production and Marketing Administration, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Production and Marketing Administration, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Production and Marketing Administration, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Production and Marketing Administration, Cotton, Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Production and Marketing Administration, Reports, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Proposed Peanut Laboratory, Dawson, Georgia, Article and Proposal, 1962, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Regulations, 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Removal of Divisions in Policy Office, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Report, “A Review of Forest and Rangeland Research Policies in the United States”, 1977 September (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Report, “Economics of Rural Ambulance Service in the Great Plains”, 1975 November (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Report, “Progress and Plans for Implementation of Rural Development Act of 1972”, 1973 April 11 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Report, “The Bird Business: A Study of the Importation of Birds into the United States”, 1977 July (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Reports and Statements, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Reports and Statements, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Reports and Resolutions, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Reports and Statements, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1966, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Reports and Statements, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Resolutions and Statements, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Resolutions, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Resolutions, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Resolutions, 1970-1972 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Rural Communities Development, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Rural Communities Development, Newsletters, 1968-1970 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Rural Development Service, Correspondence and Pamphlet, 1975-1978 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Rural Development Service, “Facts on Rural Development Resources”, 1974-1977 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Rural Development Service, Pamphlets and Statements, 1972-1974 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Rural Development Service, Rural Community Fire Protection, Correspondence and Fact Sheet, 1972-1975 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Rural Job Development Act, Summaries, circa 1969 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Scrapie, Report, 1960 June (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Secretary of Agriculture, Statements (1 of 2), 1953-1958 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Secretary of Agriculture, Statements (2 of 2), 1953-1958 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Skip-Row Planting, Correspondence and Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Articles and Mailing Lists, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Bills and Reports, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Clippings and Reports, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Coleman County, Soil Surveys, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence and Report, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence and Reports, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence and Clippings, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence and Clippings, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence and Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence and Minutes, 1972-1976 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Correspondence and Maps, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Flood Prevention, Map and Statement, 1950, undated (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Soil Conservation Service, George H. Edgerton, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Soil Conservation Service, “Guidelines for Developing State Plans for U.S. Agricultural Service Centers”, 1974-1976 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Howard Boswell, Correspondence and Report, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Jack Browder, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Map, “Organized Soil Conservation Districts in Texas”, 1941 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Maps, 1950-1951 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Soil Conservation Service, McLennan County, Soil Surveys, Correspondence, 1959 August (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Milam County Soil Surveys, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Pamphlets, 1949-1951 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Press Releases and Reports, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Press Releases and Reports, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Report, “Upstream Flood Prevention in the Western Gulf Region”, 1953 January (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Reports, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Robert Koch, Clippings and Correspondence, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Soil Bank, Correspondence, Press Releases, and Reports, 1956-1961 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Soil Conservation Service, “Soil Survey of Bell County, Texas”, 1916 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Soil Conservation Service, Soil Survey, McLennan County, Texas, 1942-1958 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Soil Conservation Service, “Watershed Progress Report”, 1977 November (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Southern Forest Experiment Station, Report, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Statements, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Statements, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Statements, 1971-1973 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Statements, 1974-1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Statistics, 1958-1959 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Sugar Act Amendments of 1962, Compendium of Statements, 1962 June 26 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Sugar Beets, Article and Press Releases, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Sugar Resolutions, Dockets (1 of 3), 1934-1936 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Sugar Resolutions, Dockets (2 of 3), 1934-1936 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Sugar Resolutions, Dockets (3 of 3), 1934-1936 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Texas Offices, Indexes (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Texas Offices, Indexes (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Texas Rural Communities, Incorporated, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Texcot Producers, Incorporated, Certificates, Correspondence, and Legal Documents, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Texcot Producers, Incorporated, Loan Application, 1964-1965 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - “The Farm Problem”, Articles, “Waco News-Tribune”, 1960 March-April (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Yearbook, “The Face of Rural America”, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Department of Commerce, 1931-1979, undated; 2
    Subseries II contains materials relating to the Department of Commerce. The bulk of the materials pertain to the Bureau of the Census and the Economic Development Administration. Topics addressed at length in the subseries include various censuses of agriculture, lists of towns in Central Texas counties, patents, community planning, trade, and financial development.
    - Aluminum Stockpiling, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Announcements, 1971-1976 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Announcements, 1977-1978 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Area Redevelopment Programs, Correspondence and Lists, 1965, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Bureau of Foreign Commerce, Guide, “Questions and Answers for Perspective Trade Mission Members”, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Mines (USBM), Circular, “Iceland Spar and Optical Fluorite”, 1931 July (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of Public Roads (BPR), Correspondence, 1952-1967 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1940 Census, Eligible Enumerators, 1939-1940 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1940 Census, Poage Recommendations (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1950 Census of Agriculture, Bell County, Texas, 1951 December 22 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1950 Census of Agriculture, Bosque County, Texas, 1951 December 26 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1950 Census of Agriculture, Coryell County, Texas, 1951 December 28 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1950 Census of Agriculture, Falls County, Texas, 1951 December 18 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1950 Census of Agriculture, McLennan County, Texas, 1951 November 13 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1950 Census of Agriculture, Milam County, Texas, 1951 November 13 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, Bell County, Texas, 1960 November (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, Bosque County, Texas, 1960 November (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, Coryell County, Texas, 1960 November (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, Falls County, Texas, 1960 November (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, Forty-Eight States, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, McLennan County, Texas, 1960 December (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, Milam County, Texas, 1960 November (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1959 Census of Agriculture, State of Texas, 1960 December (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1960 Census, Texas Report, 1961 March 30 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1970 Census, Advance Report, 1971 January (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1970 Census, Clippings (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1970 Census, Questions, 1968-1970 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1970 Census, Supplementary Report, 1976 October (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1972 Census of Construction Industries, Preliminary Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of the Census, Clippings and Press Releases, 1971-1976 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of the Census, Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Bureau of the Census, Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of the Census, Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of the Census, Correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Bureau of the Census, Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Bureau of the Census, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Bureau of the Census, “Current Population Reports”, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Bureau of the Census, “Current Population Reports”, 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of the Census, “Current Population Reports”, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of the Census, “Factfinder for the Nation”, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, General, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Bell County, 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Bosque County, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Coryell County, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Falls County, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Hood County, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Limestone County, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, McLennan County, 1966-1971 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Milam County, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Parker County, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Robertson County, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of the Census, List of Towns, Somervell County, 1967-1971 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Bureau of the Census, “Mini-Guide to the 1972 Economic Censuses”, 1973 November (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Bureau of the Census, Newsletters and Remarks, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Bureau of the Census, Population of Voting Age, Press Releases and Reports, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Bureau of the Census, Press Releases, 1958-1961 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of the Census, Press Releases, Reports, and Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of the Census, Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Bureau of the Census, Supplementary Report, “Race of the Population by County: 1970”, 1975 December (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - “Community Planning Problems in Federal Grant Programs”, Recommendations, 1967 December (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Contacts and Printed Materials, circa 1976-1977 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1952-1953 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Announcements and Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Atlas of Planning Jurisdictions (1 of 2), 1966-1968 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Atlas of Planning Jurisdictions (2 of 2), 1966-1968 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Booklet, “They Did ItELWhy Not You?”, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Brochures, 1965-1966 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Clippings and Press Releases, 1966-1969 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Data for Representatives and Senators, circa 1960s (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), “Directory of Approved Projects”, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), “Guide for Area Overall Economic Development Programs”, 1969 October (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), “Guidelines for Local Public Works Capital Development and Investment Program”, 1976 August 23 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), “Guidelines for Round 2 of the Local Public Works Program”, 1977 June 6 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), List of Development Districts, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Press Releases and Resolutions, 1970-1973 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Press Releases, 1975-1978 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Report, “Maximum Grant Rates for Public Works Grants in Qualified Areas”, 1966 July 1 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Reports, 1965-1969 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Economic Development Administration (EDA), Elizabeth Krause, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Footwear Industry Revitalization Program, Annual Report, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Life Safety, Correspondence and Programs, 1978-1979 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - National Bureau of Standards, “American Softwood Lumber Standard”, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - National Bureau of Standards, Pamphlets, 1974-1977 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - National Bureau of Standards, Report, “What About Metric?”, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), Report, “The Federal Plan for Meteorological Services and Supporting Research”, 1978 July (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), Reports, “Major Abnormal Weather Conditions Affecting World Agriculture”, 1978-1979 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), Sea Grant Annual Report, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - National Technical Information Service, Periodicals, “Health Planning”, 1978 March-June (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - National Technical Information Service (NTIS), Report, Interagency Task Force on Product Liability, circa 1977 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Office of Energy Programs, Booklet, “Energy: Critical Choices Ahead”, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Office of Federal Statistical Policy and Standards, “Standard Metropolitan Statistical Classification”, 1978 October 24 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Office of Minority Business Enterprise, Clippings, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Patent Office, Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Patent Office, Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Patent Office, Correspondence and Petitions, 1965-1978 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Patent Office, Information Concerning Patents and Trademarks, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 18)